Great.
Great. Just give me a sec
to change film.
I know I'm not
supposed to know
but I do.
I'm so excited
for you.
What's going on?
Monica's pregnant!
Oh, my God.
Is that why you guys
had to get married?
Guys, I'm not pregnant.
Oh. Slow swimmers?
What?
What do you mean?
You're not pregnant?
You didn't tell anybody
I was, did you?
No. I'll be right back.
Now, why don't
we get a shot
of just Monica
and the bloody soldier?
About that, Joey,
you have to change
before the party.
I can't. I don't have
any other clothes here.
Find some, please?
Anything that doesn't say,
"I died tragically in France."
Then why don't
we see the bride
and the groom
and the bridesmaids?
Okay.
Hey, Mon, why'd
you tell the guys
that you weren't pregnant?
Because I'm not.
We found your test
in the trash.
If you're not pregnant...
...it's because I am.
What are you
talking about?
Yes, I am...
I am with child.
And I didn't want
to say anything
because it's your day.
I didn't want
to steal your thunder.
Wait a minute.
So you told people
I was pregnant?
Does this look like
a conversation
I want to remember?
Who's the father?
Yeah.
I can't say.
Why?
Why not?
I can't say because he's famous.
Oh, my God.
Who is it?
Phoebe, come on.
You have to tell us.
Okay, okay.
It's James Brolin.
James Brolin is the father
of my baby.
As in Barbra Streisand's
husband James Brolin?
What? Well, he never said that
to me.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day ♪
♪ Your week, your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me too. ♪
Monica, if you
could step away
we'll get Chandler
and the bridesmaids.
How about just
the bridesmaids?
You know,
I am the groom.
I was told it was
kind of a big deal.
It is.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for
doing that.
I just can't deal
with this stress
quite yet.
So instead you told me
Monica was pregnant?
You said that she was.
I just didn't
disagree with you.
Sneaky.
Yeah.
Smile, ladies.
Oh, by the way,
James Brolin?
Oh, I know.
I could only think
of two names.
Him and Ed Begley, Jr.
and then...
I remembered
he's gay, so...
Ed Begley, Jr.
is not gay.
Really?
Thank you very much.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it gives me great pleasure
to introduce to you
for the very first time
Mr. and Mrs. Chandler Bing.
Listen, before we go
out there
I got a present
for you.
Honey, I'm not going
to put my hand
in your pocket.
No.
No?
I've been taking
dancing lessons.
What?
Yeah, for the last
six weeks.
I wanted this to be a moment
you would never forget.
That is so sweet.
So, would you care
to join me
in our first dance
as husband and wife?
Yes.
Okay.
What's the matter?
It's these new shoes.
They're all slippery.
Are you going to be
able to do this?
Not well.
Well, the good news is
I don't think
anyone's looking at us.
So, you ready
to talk about it?
No.
Now?
Okay, we'll talk
about something else, then.
Okay.
Who's the father?
Oh!
Look, honey, I haven't
told him yet
so until I do
I don't think I should
tell anybody else.
Yeah. That's fine.
That's fair.
Thank you.
Is it Tag?
Oh! Phoebe!
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'll stop.
Okay.
Is it Ross?
It's Ross, isn't it?
Oh, my God!
It's Joey!
Honey, stop it, okay?
I am not going
to tell you
until I tell him.
Aha! At least we know
it's a him.
Oh, sweet Lord.
I'm sorry, okay?
I went down
to the gift shop
and it was either this
or a bathrobe.
Look, what's
more important:
the way I'm dressed
or me being with you
on your special day?
Honey, I'm not going
to even pretend
I was listening.
Hey, hey.
Hi.
I'm Ross.
I don't believe we met.
I'm Monica's older brother.
Oh, hi. I'm Mona
from her restaurant.
Oh.
Hello, Mona
from her restaurant.
Mona, what a beautiful name.
You think so?
I always kind of hated it.
Aw, come on. Mona Lisa?
Uh-huh.
Mona... Kleckklecken.
The famous botanist, huh?
Oh, no, she's...
Well, she's
dead now, but...
Supposedly she was
once quite the hottie
of the plant world.
Really?
Well, see, I never knew
about her.
Linda Kleckklecken.
So what.. what table
are you at?
Oh, me, too.
Good. Now there'll be someone
there who likes my name.
Yes, there will.
Oh, guess what, Molly Gilbert.
You've just been bumped up
to table one
and if it's all right
with you
I'm going to take your place
at table six.
Martin Kleckklecken.
That's better.
Now bend you arms
a little bit.
There you go. Okay.
Look straight ahead.
Now, this time
I want you
to really put
your ass into it.
Yeah.
Chandler, darling, look,
my date has finally arrived.
I'd like you to meet
Dennis Phillips.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yes, Dennis, is
a dear old friend
and a fantastic lover.
Bravo, Dennis.
Thanks for pleasing
my mother so.
Oh, I'm so sorry
I missed the ceremony.
I was stuck at auditions.
Oh, yes. Dennis is directing
a new Broadway show.
I don't believe we've met.
Joey Tribbiani.
Dennis Philipps.
Oh, wow, I've admired
your work for years.
You've done some
really amazing stuff.
Oh, thank you.
Well, if you'll
excuse me
I'm going to go
get myself a drink.
I'll be back
in a moment.
Wow, Dennis Phillips.
That's great.
How did you guys meet?
Well, you know,
it's a funny story.
Funny ha-ha
or funny...
( imitates gunshot )
Uh-oh!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Now if everyone will please
take your seats
dinner will be served.
Hey, I thought you
were at table six.
Uh, no, nine.
Oh, see
before when you
showed it to me
you held it
that way, which...
( chuckles )
...which was misleading.
Well...
Hello.
Hey, Chandler.
Hey.
Will you see
if your mom
will give my resume
to Dennis Phillips?
'Cause if I could get
in a Broadway show
then I would have done it all:
film, television and theater.
The only thing left
would be radio
and that's just
for ugly people.
What size shoes
do you wear?
Uh, 11... 11 1/2.
Great, because my shoes are
giving me a little problem.
Could I borrow the boots
from your costume?
I don't even really know
where I left those.
Huh. Sorry.
Those aren't 11 1/2.
Okay, fine. I'm a 7.
All right? I have
surprisingly small feet.
But the rest of me is good.
I'll show you.
Can you believe
Phoebe got pregnant?
Oh, you know what, honey?
Let's not talk
about that right now.
This is so huge!
Sure, but come on,
as big as your wedding?
Of course not.
Nothing is.
Well, between me and you?
Yeah.
In this day and age
how dumb do you have to be
to get pregnant?
Hey, you know,
sometimes you can
do everything right.
Everyone can wear
everything they're
supposed to wear
and one of those little
guys just gets through.
How?
I don't know.
Maybe they have tools.
Well, I-I talked to her
and, uh, she's definitely
going to have this baby.
You know, she said she's going
to raise it on her own.
Well, maybe that's...
maybe that's really brave.
Maybe.
I just hope she realizes
how hard it's going to be.
Maybe she hasn't really
thought it through
that much.
Well, there's a lot
to think about.
I mean, how is she...
how is she going
to handle this financially?
How is she going
to juggle work? How...?
Does she realize
she's not going
to have a date again
for the next, like, 18 years?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
I'm just thinking
about Phoebe.
Poor, knocked-up Phoebe.
Champagne?
Oh, yes, thank you
very much. Ooh!
Oh, th-th-that's actually
how the French drink it.
( gasps )
Well...
I just got off the phone
with my lover, James Brolin.
Oh, really?
Yes. And apparently
he is married to some singer.
But he said
he would leave her for me
and I said, "James,
James Brolin, are you sure?"
And James Brolin said...
"Rachel's really
the one who's pregnant"?
What?!
Why bother?
( sighs )
How do you feel?
I don't know.
I don't know
how I feel.
This is all
happening so fast.
I have to make all
these decisions
that I don't
want to make.
Mm! Oh, someone
just take this
away from me!
Calm down.
Maybe you're
not pregnant.
What?!
When I got pregnant
with the triplets
I took that test, like,
three times just to make sure.
Yes, maybe it's
a false positive.
Are you sure you peed
on the stick right?
How many ways
are there to do that?
I'm-I'm just saying
don't freak out
until you're 100% sure.
All right, I'll-I'll take it
again when I get home.
You-you got
to take it now.
Now, come on,
do it as a present to me.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
I'll run out and get you one.
Oh, you girls
are so great.
Oh, wait a minute.
Who's the father?
Oh, no,
she won't tell us.
Come on. It's my wedding.
That could be my present.
Wait. Hey, I just gave
you peeing on a stick.
See, this is
why you register.
( farting )
( giggling )
It was the chair again, okay?
I'm not doing it.
Hey, what, look, I don't...
You know what?
( chuckles )
Hi.
Um, would you
like to dance?
Sure.
Huh?
Oh, great.
( chuckles )
Dr. Geller?
I wasn't farting!
Uh, a little game
from our table.
Oh.
Yes?
Dr. Geller,
will you dance with me?
Oh. Um... well, uh,
maybe-maybe later.
Right now, I'm about
to dance with this lady.
( softly ):
Okay.
Oh...
Well, uh-uh...
unless, um...
unless...
uh, this lady wouldn't mind
letting you go first.
I'd be happy to.
You are very sweet.
( chuckling ):
Oh... yes, I-I am.
In fact, um, hey, why don't
we try it my special way
and you could dance on my feet?
Sure!
Yeah?
Hop on.
Is the pretty lady looking?
Uh-huh.
Keep dancing.
And the world will never know.
Hey, did you talk to Dennis
about me yet?
Yes. I told him
how talented you were.
I told him all about
Days of Our Lives.
No, no, no, no!
You don't tell
a Broadway guy that!
Now he thinks
I'm just a soap actor.
But you're not
just a soap actor.
You are a soap actor with
freakishly tiny feet.
Hey!
Thank you.
No, no, thank you, Miranda.
Melinda.
All right.
How cute was that?
Oh, oh, were you...
were you watching?
( chuckling )
Can I go next?
Uh... of course you can.
Hop on.
Okay, but I get to hop on
after her.
( under breath ):
I am so going to score.
What?
I like your bow.
( clinking )
I'd, uh...
I'd like to propose a toast.
To Monica
and Chandler--
the greatest couple
in the world...
and my best friends.
Now, when I first found out
they were getting married
I was...
I was a little angry.
I was, like, "Why, God, why?!
How can you take them away
from me?!"
But then I
thought back
over all our memories together.
Some happy memories.
( chuckling )
And-and there was
some sad memories.
( sniffles )
I'm sorry.
And-and some scared memories.
Whoa!
Huh?
And then... and then I realized
I'll always be their friend--
their friend who can speak
in many dialects
and has training in stage combat
and is willing to do
partial nudity.
Oh, to the happy couple.
All right.
( applause )
That was very nice, Ashley.
Can we do it again?
No, no.
So...
is it my turn now?
I'm next.
Oh!
Uh...
that's okay.
You can dance
with her first.
Oh, you're-you're sure?
Okay.
Okay, so what's, uh,
what's your name?
Gert.
That's-that's pretty.
Yes.
Wa...?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
( chuckling )
What are you doing there, Gert?
Dancing on your feet
like the other
girls did it.
Okay.
Hop on, Gert.
( crunching )
Why aren't you
moving your feet?
I'm trying.
Faster!
You're not going
fast enough!
Maybe I should stand
on your feet!
So, did you, uh
happen to catch
my toast up there?
Oh, my God.
That was for my benefit?
Well, I like to think there was
a little something for everyone
but I know you're casting
for this new show...
Look, um
Joey, I-I don't think you're
quite right for this project.
Oh, see, that's
where you're wrong.
Whatever it is, I can do it.
And if you didn't
see it up there
just-just try me.
It's an all-Chinese cast.
Can you be Chinese?
Well, I'm not proud
of this, but..
Oh, my God, no, no, no,
please, please don't, don't...!
( laughter )
Hey. You ready to get
back on the dance floor?
Did it turn into sand?
Oh, come on.
I love this song.
Come on.
You'll be fine.
No, no... I won't.
Do you know why
I took all those lessons?
See, for the first time
I didn't want you
to be embarrassed
to be seen on the dance floor
with some... clumsy idiot.
Oh, sweetie, you could
never embarrass me.
( snickers )
Okay.
You could easily
embarrass me
but come on,
it doesn't matter.
All right?
I married you.
So, I want to dance
on my wedding night
with my husband,
come on.
Just try not to move
your feet at all.
Oh.
There you go.
Chandler, I'm going
to have you arrested.
Why?
You stole my moves!
How much longer?
30 seconds.
30 seconds, okay.
Did I miss it?
Rachel?
I-I want you to know that...
if it's positive,
we're going to...
Oh, I know, I know.
You do?
Mm-hmm.
It's time.
Oh, boy.
ALL:
No!
( door closes )
All right.
Go ahead, Rach.
Oh, wait, you know what?
I can't...
I can't look at it.
Somebody else tell me.
Somebody tell me.
Okay.
Um...
It's negative.
What?!
Oh?
Oh.
( chuckles )
Well, there you go.
Whew!
That is... that's great.
That is really great,
great news.
( Rachel sighs )
You know, 'cause the whole...
uh, not being ready
and kind of financial aspects,
all that's...
( sighs )
Wow, this is so just the way
that this was supposed to be.
( sighs )
Well... then great.
Mm-hmm.
Here.
Thanks. God, this is so stupid!
How can I be upset
over something I never had?
It's negative?
No, it's positive.
What?!
It's-It's not negative.
It's positive.
Are you sure?
Well, yeah,
I lied before.
Oh...!
Oh.
Oh, my God.
( whimpering )
Now you know how
you really feel about it.
Oh, that's a risky little game.
( Rachel laughs )
Are you really
going to do this?
Yeah.
I'm going to have a baby.
I'm going to
have a baby.
( chuckles )
I'm going to have a baby!
Yeah!
Oh!
With who?
Oh, it's still
not the time.
( giggling )
I just didn't see
the fast song coming.
Shh, shh,
don't try to talk.
We'll get you
up to your room.
We'll soak your feet.
You'll be okay.
Ah, thank you.
That is so sweet.
Yeah.
No, I mean it.
There are so few
genuinely nice guys out there.
Oh, tell me about it.
I feel like
I'm holding down the fort
all by myself.
It's Joey, right?
Yeah.
Wait a minute! No!
I'm the nice one!
I'm the one who danced
with the kids all night!
I...
How small are your feet?!